Please, Man of God, help my son; he has a permanent erection since December 25th.
Man of God, help my son!
Please, Man of God, help me! I'm having a permanent erection.
It has been like this since last year. Man of God, help me!
Man of God, help me!
What happened to you?
I slept with a prostitute, Man of God!
You went to a prostitute?
Yes.
How much did you pay?
500 naira, Man of God.
Healing In Jesus' Name
Stand up!
He's free; take him to the toilet.
After Prophet T.B. Joshua prays for him in the power of the Holy Ghost, he instructs him to go to the toilet
and urinate the poisonous substance that held his manhood.
Glory be to God! He's free in Jesus' name.
I told him to go and urinate. That is the poison that holds the penis.
Urinating Poisonous Substances
That is the poison.
There's no more pain. Thank You, Jesus!
Thank You, Jesus! My son is healed! Thank You, Lord!
The pain there is gone - that is the poison that was stopped (from operating).
With that, he would not be able to urinate. Now that he has urinated, it's gone.
Healed In Jesus' Name
STANDARD FOR LIFE
A little while after the prayer of Prophet T.B. Joshua, Mr Akinrinwa Sunday returned to The SCOAN
to testify of how Jesus Christ had completely healed him from the problem of a permanent erection.
The picture of tension and discomfort on the left side of the screen is an obvious difference
to the young man smiling on the right hand side.
It is clear to see that something has changed in his life after the prayer of Prophet T.B. Joshua.
The young man seen bent downward on the left,
poses to show the painful permanent erection visible even with his underwear on.
While on the right, the healed young man reveals his healthy body without any strain or discomfort.
Thanks to the miraculous healing he received in the name of Jesus Christ!
The sickness and tension which had invaded his life has been replaced with good health and relaxation.
By the grace of God, Mr Sunday even taps his private part
to show that he feels no more pain or discomfort and that God has restored him completely
To God be the glory!
TESTIMONY TIME
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Testimony Time
We can see the young man in our midst right now, full of joy. We want to listen to their testimony.
Brother, you're welcome. Please introduce yourself to us and the gentleman beside you.
My name is Akinrinwa Sunday and the person beside me is my father.
The problem that brought me to The SCOAN was a permanent erection for five months.
What happened that day was that my friends and I went out and I met with a prostitute.
After meeting with the prostitute, I went back home and entered the kitchen to eat.
After eating, I went upstairs to the toilet.
On coming out of the toilet, a strong breeze blew on me and I collapsed immediately.
Unfortunately, I found myself the next day in a hospital.
When I woke up, I had pain all over my body and I had a permanent erection.
When this problem started, I had severe pain to such an extent that I couldn't get out of bed.
They gave me different medications, injections, but the erection still persisted.
The doctors in the hospital said I had to undergo an operation which my father rejected.
After my father had rejected the operation, they had to discharge me.
After being discharged, I was taken to different churches for prayers which still brought no change.
My father said that he watches Emmanuel TV all the time and this kind of problem
occurred before and the man of God solved it.
Hence, he said we should come down to The SCOAN.
Okay, brother, just before you describe what happened when you came here,
could you just tell us - for those five months that you're having this permanent erection,
just give an idea of the kind of pain you were having at that period.
The pain was so terrible! When I woke up, I couldn't get off the bed.
To sit down or lay down was a problem; I had pain all over my body.
I couldn't withstand the pain; I couldn't go out nor put on anything.
So, for those five months, you were basically in your house unable to move about or do anything
because of the severity of those pains.
I couldn't go out or do anything at all; I was just laying on the bed for five months.
When I was brought to The SCOAN, the man of God immediately stretched forth his hand towards me,
my manhood began to shake and I felt a cool breeze on me.
The pain left my body immediately and the man of God told me to go and urinate.
He said the poison will be removed through urination.
Immediately, the pain left after I urinated!
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
We want you to explain again, brother. You mean as the the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua,
began to pray for you, physically, your private part began to vibrate as the spirit of God started touching you?
Yes, my manhood began to vibrate and shake as if there were some objects inside it.
I just give glory to God!
Then afterwards, we saw that you urinated out this poisonous substance.
Tell us, ever since that encounter two weeks ago here in The SCOAN, what has happened?
After urinating, immediately the pain left me; I don't feel it anymore.
The permanent erection went down and my manhood is normal now.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
We listened to our brother. He said that after he urinated out that poisonous substance, the pain left
and slowly but surely that permanent erection began to reduce, until the point where it was no longer a problem to him.
It was normal. Since then his erection has come down and he's now living a normal life.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ one more time!
Brother, you mean to say that the pain has gone? You've been walking, moving around,
eating freely, sleeping well since that deliverance?
After I received a touch from the man of God that day, I slept like a baby!
I can walk around, jump and do all sorts of things I couldn't do before.
I give glory to God.
Amen! Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Just to the glory of God: Can you just show us the things you can now do that you couldn't do before
and just quickly move in our midst to show us?
Before I couldn't walk but now I'm walking freely; I couldn't jump but now I can jump!
I can exercise now; I am free and I give glory to God.
Before I couldn't even touch it but now I can touch it and this is it.
Mr Akinrinwa Sunday & Father
Healing Testimony
Hallelujah! Glory be to God! Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
We can see something that we'd understand, especially the men in our midst would understand.
It would be impossible for our brother to have touched the area in that manner with the permanent erection
but we can see him tapping the area without any pain.
Walking freely, even jumping in the midst of the people of God to testify that indeed, he is completely healed.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
So, right now we want to hear a quick word from your dad.
What he has to say concerning the wonderful deliverance in the life of his son.
Sir, you're welcome. Please introduce yourself to us.Tell us what you're doing for a living
and tell us more about the wonderful testimony we've heard from your son.
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Akinrinwa Oriola. I come from Ondo state, Nigeria.
I am into medicine. I am the Deputy State President of Ondo state.
The boy standing beside me is my son.
What actually happened was that on the 25th of December 2016,
when we came back from church, this boy went out.
That evening, his mother was constantly calling me.
I answered, "What's the problem? You have two matured sons at home.
If it is about the generator or fuel, they should go and get it for you".
But she kept on calling me and when I picked it up this time, I heard people shouting,
"In Jesus' name", so I took a vehicle and went back home.
On reaching home, I met my young boy that is in UniBen struggling; I got so confused!
We decided to take him to a specialist hospital where doctors battled with his problem.
We didn't know then what was actually happening.
On the second day we discovered that the boy had a permanent erection.
After a lot of medications from here and there, we sat down with some of my close friends;
discussing his case and they suggested that it's better for the boy to undergo surgery.
I said to myself that this was over 48 hours, and anything done after such a time would be 50/50.
I have been watching Emmanuel TV and last year a man with a similar problem was delivered.
I said to myself that my son's problem is not exceptional; we have to be there.
I believed that this will be my last bus stop.
Two weeks ago, I brought the boy down to The SCOAN and the man of God prayed for him,
today, it's a thing of the past!
Amen! Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Tell us, since those two weeks that your son received his healing here, what are the changes you've seen
and what can you testify about him as a father?
There were a lot of changes for him; I had to divide the semester for him.
He is a university student of science and technology but due to that problem,
we had to postpone the semester whereby it's still pending; it's about his education.
About other activities, he was more or less an incomplete human being because
the ability to move and do something was zero, due to the severe pains he was experiencing.
The more the problem persisted, the more he deteriorated day by day.
He would wrestle with the problem until he slumbered and we would rush him to the hospital.
Today, it's a new dawn for him.
Hallelujah! Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Amen! Glory be to God Almighty. What is your word of advice to our viewers
especially as you introduced yourself as someone in the medical field?
We know you tried your best medically to treat such a case, even to the extent of preparing for an operation.
But to the glory of God you came here and Jesus Christ intervened.
So what is your word of advice to viewers all over the world?
Thank you, sir. This is a big lesson for the young ones.
When your parents take you to school, you should focus and concentrate.
Work as if everything depends on you and pray as if everything depends on God. Thank you.
Amen! Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Let's just hear a final word from our brother. What is your own word of advice?
You have heard it from your father - just earlier, a word of warning for young ones out there.
As someone that has passed through this amount of pain for five months after meeting a prostitute,
what is your own word of advice to our viewers all over the world?
My word of advice to the youths out there is that they should stay away from fornication and adultery,
they should move closer to God in any situation they find themselves in,
and not further away from Him.
Amen! Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ one more time!